tomwoodproject.com 2016-05-29

# Privacy statement – Tom Wood AS

By using our services you are providing certain personal data to us. We only retain and use the personal data provided directly by you or for which it is clear that it has been supplied to us to be processed. Your privacy is of great importance to us. Therefor we process your personal data with the utmost care and in compliance with the requirements laid down by the Norwegian Personal Data Protection Act (DPDA). We will not provide any personal data to third parties without your permission.

This privacy statement was last amended on the 3rd of September 2014.

 ORDERS  
We use the following data to process orders:

\- Name and address   
\- Telephone number  
\- Billing address  
\- Email address  
\- Payment details

 NEWSLETTER  
We have a newsletter to inform those interested of our products. Your email address will be added to the list of subscribers with your explicit consent only. Each newsletter contains a link to unsubscribe from our newsletter.

 REGISTRATION  
Certain features of our services require you to register beforehand. After your registration we will retain your user name and the personal data you provided so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our website, to contact you in connection with the execution of the agreement, invoicing and payment, and to provide an overview of the products and services you have purchased from us.  
We will not provide the data linked to your user name to third parties, unless it is necessary for the execution of the agreement you concluded with us or if this is required by law. In the event of suspicion of fraud or misuse of our website we may hand over personal data to the entitled authorities.  
To register on our website we require the following data:

\- Name and address  
\- Telephone number  
\- Email address   
\- Payment details

 COOKIES  
In order to provide you with optimum service we may use cookies. Cookies are small text files that can be read by a webserver in the domain that put the cookie on your hard drive. Cookies are used to store your preferences and settings.

 GOOGLE ANALYTICS  
To compile analytics, such as how often users visit our website and what pages they visit when they do so, we use Google Analytics. Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the website. We only use the information we get from Google Analytics to maintain and improve our website’s technical performance. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. 

 SOCIAL MEDIA BUTTONS  
This website features social media buttons. These buttons are used by the providers of these services to collect your personal data.

 THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES  
This statement is not applicable to third-party websites connected to this website through links. We cannot guarantee that these third parties will handle your personal data in a secure and careful manner. We recommend you read these websites’ privacy statements before making use of these websites.

 SECURITY  
We take security measures to reduce misuse of and unauthorized access to personal data. We do keep statistics on our website, giving us access to individual data. However, we only access individual data insofar as necessary for the purposes set out in this statement.

 CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT  
We reserve the right to modify this statement at all times.

 Please contact us if you have any questions regarding to our privacy policy or if you wish to review, modify or delete your personal data.
